{
    "id": "d3ecfcc6382c454db5a528625eb21237",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The lecture was so interesting that the audience sat ……………………….",
            "description": "Here the adjective motionless describes the noun audience, not their sitting. ",
            "answers": [
                "motionless",
                "motionlessly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie I watched yesterday was ………………………….. boring.",
            "description": "Fairly is not normally used with negative ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather",
                "fairly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju worked ……………………. to succeed.",
            "description": "Hard can be an adjective and an adverb hardly is similar to scarcely. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The ointment ………………………….. his pain.",
            "description": "To alleviate pain is to lessen pain. ",
            "answers": [
                "alleviated",
                "alluviated",
                "allied"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a ………………………… woman.",
            "description": "Virtuous means pious. ",
            "answers": [
                "virtual",
                "virtuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My hen …………………………. twenty eggs last month.",
            "description": "When lie means recline, its past tense is lay. Hens lay eggs. The past tense of lay is laid. ",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lay",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is always ……………………….. towards his teachers and elders.",
            "description": "Respectful means showing respect respectable means worthy of being respected. ",
            "answers": [
                "respectable",
                "respectful"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They tried to solve the dispute …………………………..",
            "description": "Amiable refers to the friendly disposition of people amicable refers to goodwill.",
            "answers": [
                "amiably",
                "amicably"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We may ……………………….. the game.",
            "description": "Loose is the opposite of tight. ",
            "answers": [
                "lose",
                "loose"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would have loved to invite all of my friends to my wedding but it was not ……………………………",
            "description": "Practicable means that can be put into practice. ",
            "answers": [
                "practical",
                "practicable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave a ………………………… account of rural India.",
            "description": "Masterly means thorough or authoritative.",
            "answers": [
                "masterful",
                "masterly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Gandhi believed in the ……………………………. of truth and non-violence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "principals",
                "principles"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}